Commencement Programs; Collection ua935
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Commencement Programs Collection1857-2014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany
ua935
1.67 cubic ft.
This collection is made up of programs for commencement ceremonies at the University at Albany.
Administrative History
Commencement programs have been issued by the University at Albany and the previous institutions it existed as for many years. Early version from the State Normal School were fairly simple, listing attending staff, some of the musical selections, and the short list of graduates that might take up a single page. They have expanded greatly since then, not only because of the growth in students and faculty at the institution, as well as the expanded nature of the event.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of the programs for commencement ceremonies from the years 1857 to 2014. The years 1957-1908 are not complete, with various copies missing. From 1910 on every version is in the collection, with the inclusion of the winter commencement programs beginning in 2001. Within these programs can be found complete lists of graduates of each various program, faculty attendees, and the speakers who delivered speeches during the ceremony.
Arrangement of the Collection
Collection is arranged chronologically.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Related Materials
Related collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives can be found in the subject guide for Criminal Justice and Prisons.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Commencement ceremonies; Baccalaureate addresses; UAlbany Reference Collections
- Commencement Programs, 1857 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- Commencement Programs, 1860 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- Commencement Programs, 1861 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- Commencement Programs, 1863 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- Commencement Programs, 1865 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- Commencement Programs, 1872 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 2)
- Commencement Programs, 1873 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 2)
- Commencement Programs, 1875 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 2)
- Commencement Programs, 1876 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 2)
- Commencement Programs, 1877 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 2)
- Commencement Programs, 1882 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 3)
- Commencement Programs, 1885 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 3)
- Commencement Programs, 1886 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 3)
- Commencement Programs, 1887 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 3)
- Commencement Programs, 1890 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 3)
- Commencement Programs, 1891 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 4)
- Commencement Programs, 1892 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 4)
- Commencement Programs, 1893 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 4)
- Commencement Programs, 1894 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 4)
- Commencement Programs, 1895 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 4)
- Commencement Programs, 1896 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 5)
- Commencement Programs, 1897 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 5)
- Commencement Programs, 1898 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 5)
- Commencement Programs, 1899 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 5)
- Commencement Programs, 1900 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 5)
- Commencement Programs, 1901 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 6)
- Commencement Programs, 1902 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 6)
- Commencement Programs, 1903 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 6)
- Commencement Programs, 1904 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 6)
- Commencement Programs, 1905 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 6)
- Commencement Programs, 1906 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 7)
- Commencement Programs, 1907 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 7)
- Commencement Programs, 1908 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 7)
- Commencement Programs, 1910 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 7)
- Commencement Programs, 1911 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 7)
- Commencement Programs, 1912 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 8)
- Commencement Programs, 1913 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 8)
- Commencement Programs, 1914 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 8)
- Commencement Programs, 1915 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 8)
- Commencement Programs, 1916 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 8)
- Commencement Programs, 1917 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 8)
- Commencement Programs, 1918 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1919 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1920 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1921 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1922 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1923 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1924 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1925 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1926 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1927 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1928 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1929 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1930 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1931 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1932 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1933 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1934 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1935 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1936 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1937 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1938 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1939 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1940 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1941 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1942 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1943 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1944 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1945 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1946 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1947 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1948 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1949 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1950 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1951 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1952 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1953 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1954 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1955 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1956 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1957 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1958 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1959 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1960 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1961 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1962 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1963 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1964 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1965 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1966 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1967 (Box 1 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1968 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- Commencement Programs, 1969 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- Commencement Programs, 1970 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- Commencement Programs, 1971 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- Commencement Programs, 1972 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- Commencement Programs, 1973 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- Commencement Programs, 1974 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 2)
- Commencement Programs, 1975 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 2)
- Commencement Programs, 1976 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 2)
- Commencement Programs, 1977 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 2)
- Commencement Programs, 1978 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 2)
- Commencement Programs, 1979 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 3)
- Commencement Programs, 1980 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 3)
- Commencement Programs, 1981 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 3)
- Commencement Programs, 1982 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 3)
- Commencement Programs, 1983 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 3)
- Commencement Programs, 1984 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 4)
- Commencement Programs, 1985 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 5)
- Commencement Programs, 1986 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 6)
- Commencement Programs, 1987 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 7)
- Commencement Programs, 1988 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 8)
- Commencement Programs, 1989 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- Commencement Programs, 1990 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- Commencement Programs, 1991 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- Commencement Programs, 1992 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 12)
- Commencement Programs, 1993 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 13)
- Commencement Programs, 1994 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 14)
- Commencement Programs, 1995 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 15)
- Commencement Programs, 1996 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 16)
- Commencement Programs, 1997 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 17)
- Commencement Programs, 1998 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 18)
- Commencement Programs, 1999 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 19)
- Commencement Programs, 2000 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 20)
- Commencement Programs, 2001 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 21)
- December Commencement Programs, 2001 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 22)
- Commencement Programs, 2002 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 23)
- December Commencement Programs, 2002 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 24)
- Commencement Programs, 2003 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 25)
- December Commencement Programs, 2003 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 26)
- Commencement Programs, 2004 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 27)
- Commencement Programs, 2005 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 28)
- December Commencement Programs, 2005 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 29)
- Commencement Programs, 2006 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 30)
- December Commencement Programs, 2006 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 31)
- Commencement Programs, 2007 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 32)
- December Commencement Programs, 2007 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 33)
- Commencement Programs, 2008 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 34)
- Commencement Platform Party Script, 2008 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 35)
- December Commencement Programs, 2008 (Box 2 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 36)
- Commencement Programs, 2009 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 1)
- December Commencement Programs, 2009 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 2)
- Commencement Programs, 2010 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 3)
- December Commencement Programs, 2010 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 4)
- Commencement Programs, 2011 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 5)
- December Commencement Programs, 2011 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 6)
- Commencement Programs, 2012 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 7)
- December Commencement Programs, 2012 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 8)
- Commencement Programs, 2013 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 9)
- December Commencement Programs, 2013 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 10)
- December Commencement Programs, 2014 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 11)
- December Commencement Program, 2016 (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection), Folder 12)
- Commencement Programs [2], 2017 May (Box 3 (Commencement Programs Collection))